<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PerfectGymCoach</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="statistics">Statistics</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="coming_next">Coming next</string>
    <string name="other_programs">Other programs</string>
    <string name="add_program">Add a program</string>
    <string name="main">Main</string>
    <string name="change_plan">Change plan</string>
    <string name="manage_workout_plans">Manage workout plans</string>
    <string name="empty_plans">This is where your workout plans will be shown, use the button below to create one!</string>
    <string name="workout">Workout</string>
    <string name="empty_programs">This is where your programs (single day schedule) will be shown, use the button below to create one!</string>
    <string name="add_exercise">Add exercise</string>
    <string name="exercises_by_muscle">Exercises by muscle</string>
    <string name="view_exercises">View exercises</string>
    <string name="empty_exercises">This is where your exercises will be shown, use the button below to add one!</string>
    <string name="current_plan">Current Plan</string>
    <string name="empty_home">You have yet to create a workout plan, use the button below to create one!</string>
    <string name="empty_home_program">The workout plan you has selected as current has no programs (single day schedule) inside. Use the button below to select a different plan or to add a program</string>
    <string name="change_workout_plan">Change workout plan</string>
    <string name="workout_empty_exercises">You have no exercises added to this program, use the button below to add some!</string>
    <string name="workout_recap">Workout recap</string>
    <string name="volume_info">The term \'volume\' in this context is used to indicate the total amount of weight lifted: Exercises x Sets x Reps x Weight. Many studies have shown the direct correlation between total volume lifted and growth in muscle. This means that in order to build bigger muscles the volume must increase either by increasing the weights, the number of reps, etc. </string>
    <string name="calories_info">The calorie consumption is calculated based on the workout time, its intensity, your body weight (don\'t forget to set it up in the Profile tab!) and some research-backed values for weight training energy consumption. NB: this calorie consumption is only approximated and may not reflect the actual consumption.</string>
    <string name="gender_info">While we support all genders and their expression, in the case of fitness activity the one that makes a difference (in performance, percentage of muscle mass, etc.) is the biological sex.</string>
    <string name="bmi_info"><![CDATA[The Body Mass Index (BMI) is a calculation used to assess a person\'s health only basing on weight and height. A value between 18.5 and 25 is considered normal, a value below 18.5 is underweight and a value above 25 until 30 is considered overweight while above 30 a person is considered obese. NB: the assessment of health is only approximated and should not be considered relevant for certain people e.g. young (<18) and elder (>65) people, bodybuilders, athletes, pregnant women, etc. Please seek medical advice if you\'re worried about your health.]]></string>
</resources>